whoozin.com 2015-04-10

# Free RSVP Online | Track RSVP’s and registrations for your events and recurring meetings.

##  Whoozin Privacy Policy

Last updated: October 1, 2012

Thinkpuddle Inc. (“Thinkpuddle”, “we”, “us”, “our”) offers various online functionality, products and services that are accessible to you through its Whoozin product line including its website located at www.whoozin.com (together with any successor site(s) and related mobile and desktop applications) (hereinafter, “Functionality”).

Preserving your privacy is very important to us. We are dedicated to providing you with superior service while protecting your privacy and safeguarding personal information. We maintain strict personal information privacy policies and use state of the art technologies to safeguard personal information and customer communications from unauthorized intrusions.

We regularly review all of our policies and procedures and will promptly post any changes to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and it is your responsibility to check for such updates.

We may collect personal information that can identify you such as your name and email address and other information that you provide to us. We may also collect information that does not identify you. When you provide personal information through our Functionality, the information may be sent to servers located in Canada, the United States and other countries around the world.

We may collect and store any personal information you enter through our Functionality or provide to us in some other manner. This includes information, such as your name, address, email address, image, telephone number. We also may request information about your interests and activities, your location and other demographic or profile information.

We collect and store personally identifiable information that you have voluntarily provided us when you register for an account or sign up to receive email notifications. This may include data such as your name, email address, physical address, and phone number. We use this information to provide you with access to the Functionality and to communicate with you.

We also collect and store personally identifiable information that you provide us. For example, profiles that you create in the Functionality may contain personal information. The information contained in such profiles, such as name, email address, phone number and physical address is used in a manner consistent with the Functionality. Based on your configuration of the Functionality we may display profile-related information such as attendee name to other users of the Functionality.

We will only collect personal information by fair and lawful means. We will not use or share the personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the purposes for which it was collected.

We collect or use personal information only when we provide and promote products, services, functionality and other opportunities to you, or when our functionality serves as a conduit to a third party, or when we reasonably believe that it will help administer our business. Our collection of personal information is often required in order to facilitate the functionality that you are using on our system. The type of personal information collected depends largely on the functionality that you use. In addition, such personal information collected may change over time since the range of products, services and functionality that we offer continues to expand and the technology we use continues to change. By providing us with personal information and using our functionality, you are deemed to have provided your permission to the collection and use of such information.

We may also collect usage information such as data collected by our Functionality (through technologies such as cookies). This information is used solely for enabling us to provide you with a customized online experience and to find ways to improve our offerings to you. Although cookies are widely used, it may be possible to disable cookies via your browser settings. However, in so doing, the Functionality may not function properly or optimally.

We may obtain your consent to use personal information by your express consent or we may determine that consent has been implied by the circumstances. Express consent could be in writing (for example in a signed consent, e-mail or application form), or verbally in person or over the telephone or by your actions (for example, logging into www.whoozin.com).

When we receive personal information from you that enables us to provide you with a requested product, service or functionality, your consent to allow us to deal with that personal information in a reasonable manner is implied. If you need to provide personal information about other individuals, you must first obtain their consent for these purposes prior to your disclosure to us.

Providing us with personal information is always your choice. When you use our products, services or functionality, we ask that you provide information that enables us to respond to your needs. In doing so, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure to appropriate third parties of such personal information for these purposes. You also authorize us to use and retain this personal information for as long as it may be required for the purposes described above.

You are entitled to access and verify your personal information. We will take reasonable steps to correct personal information that is not accurate.

Upon receipt of a written request, you will be able to review, within a reasonable time following such request, any personal information that is maintained in reasonably retrievable form. You may be required to provide specific identification information so that we can verify your identify before we provide you with the personal information we hold. Requests that require archival or other retrieval costs may be subject to a fee which will be communicated to you prior to retrieving the information. Access to your personal information may be denied in certain circumstances including when such denial is required or authorized by law or may have an unreasonable effect on other people’s privacy. 

We may disclose personal information without your consent in certain circumstances such as where such disclosure is: required by law; required to comply with a warrant or court order; related to an offence that has been or is about to be committed; required due to an emergency; made for the purpose of collecting a debt owed by you; protecting our rights and that of our users and third parties.

We employ physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect our systems and all personal information under our control against unauthorized access and use. However, no system can be completely secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or other information will always remain secure.

This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the Functionality.

Any inquiries should be submitted through the Functionality’s support system.
